[{"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "JJS", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "TO", "VBG", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 18, "question": "As we -- as we talk now in the middle of a nightmare, what do you make of where we really are with this?", "question_tokens": ["As", "we", "--", "as", "we", "talk", "now", "in", "the", "middle", "of", "a", "nightmare", ",", "what", "do", "you", "make", "of", "where", "we", "really", "are", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["IN", "PRP", ":", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 19, "answer": "Well, throughout most of the day, I thought they were very close to reaching a cease- fire agreement.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "throughout", "most", "of", "the", "day", ",", "I", "thought", "they", "were", "very", "close", "to", "reaching", "a", "cease-", "fire", "agreement", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["RB", "."], "qSentId": 31, "question": "What did she mean by that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "did", "she", "mean", "by", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 32, "answer": "Right.", "answer_tokens": ["Right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "JJ", "DT", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 53, "question": "What is your gut feeling about what is going on on the ground?", "question_tokens": ["What", "is", "your", "gut", "feeling", "about", "what", "is", "going", "on", "on", "the", "ground", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "WP", "VBZ", "VBG", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 54, "answer": "Well, it's nice those reactions side by side.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "'s", "nice", "those", "reactions", "side", "by", "side", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["last Wednesday"]}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", ",", "IN", "POS", "DT", "NN", "NN", "TO", "VB", ",", "IN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "EX", "VBP", "NNS", "IN", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "WP", "NNS", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "RB", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "RB", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "VB", "JJ", "NNP", "WRB", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "."], "qSentId": 71, "question": "Who do you think holds the high moral ground, if either side does right now, in terms of opinion outside of the immediate region?", "question_tokens": ["Who", "do", "you", "think", "holds", "the", "high", "moral", "ground", ",", "if", "either", "side", "does", "right", "now", ",", "in", "terms", "of", "opinion", "outside", "of", "the", "immediate", "region", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNS", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBZ", "RB", "RB", ",", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 72, "answer": "Well, I mean, that's a difficult question to ask, because certainly outside the region, there are impressions that are gleaned from the news, from what people read in the newspaper, but really, it's here where the history of this conflict doesn't begin last Wednesday when the fighting began.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "mean", ",", "that", "'s", "a", "difficult", "question", "to", "ask", ",", "because", "certainly", "outside", "the", "region", ",", "there", "are", "impressions", "that", "are", "gleaned", "from", "the", "news", ",", "from", "what", "people", "read", "in", "the", "newspaper", ",", "but", "really", ",", "it", "'s", "here", "where", "the", "history", "of", "this", "conflict", "does", "n't", "begin", "last", "Wednesday", "when", "the", "fighting", "began", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 77, "question": "Do you believe that Iran, from everything you're gleaning on the ground there, is as involved as the Israelis believe?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "believe", "that", "Iran", ",", "from", "everything", "you", "'re", "gleaning", "on", "the", "ground", "there", ",", "is", "as", "involved", "as", "the", "Israelis", "believe", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NN", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "DT", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "VBP", "."], "aSentId": 78, "answer": "Well, certainly.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "certainly", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Iran"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "VBZ", "DT", "RB", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 97, "question": "What do you think it's going to take to try and guarantee some form of cease-fire?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "take", "to", "try", "and", "guarantee", "some", "form", "of", "cease-fire", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "CC", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 98, "answer": "Well, I think this is a very serious situation.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "think", "this", "is", "a", "very", "serious", "situation", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "POS", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 136, "question": "They're two completely separate areas, aren't they?", "question_tokens": ["They", "'re", "two", "completely", "separate", "areas", ",", "are", "n't", "they", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "CD", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "VBP", "RB", "PRP", "."], "aSentId": 137, "answer": "Well, that's right.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "'s", "right", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Senate Intelligence Committee", "CIA"]}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "IN", ",", "CC", "DT", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", "VBZ", "VBN", "RB", "JJ", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "PRP", "JJ", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "DT", "TO", "NNP", "NN", "IN", ",", "CC", "WP", "VBN", "WP", "NNS", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 144, "question": "Are we any nearer to knowing the answer to that question?", "question_tokens": ["Are", "we", "any", "nearer", "to", "knowing", "the", "answer", "to", "that", "question", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "DT", "NN", "TO", "DT", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 145, "answer": "Well, we have a process in place to find that out, and the Senate Intelligence Committee has made very clear, and I made it clear in the meeting, that we want that whole process from A to Z gone through, and who made what changes from the initial analysis done by the CIA.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "have", "a", "process", "in", "place", "to", "find", "that", "out", ",", "and", "the", "Senate", "Intelligence", "Committee", "has", "made", "very", "clear", ",", "and", "I", "made", "it", "clear", "in", "the", "meeting", ",", "that", "we", "want", "that", "whole", "process", "from", "A", "to", "Z", "gone", "through", ",", "and", "who", "made", "what", "changes", "from", "the", "initial", "analysis", "done", "by", "the", "CIA", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"], "LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NN", "NN", "IN", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "JJ", "IN", "NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "RB", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "CC", "IN", "DT", "MD", "CC", "VB", "PRP", "VBP", "CC", "RB", "JJ", "NNS", "WDT", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "TO", "NN", "JJR", "IN", "PDT", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NNP", ",", "CD", "CD", "NNS", "IN", "NN", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "TO", "VB", "VBG", "IN", ",", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "NNS", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "JJ", "NNS", ",", "IN", "PRP", "MD", "."], "qSentId": 180, "question": "What does he mean, Prime Minister Netanyahu, by long- term solution and what does he mean by taking whatever action necessary?", "question_tokens": ["What", "does", "he", "mean", ",", "Prime", "Minister", "Netanyahu", ",", "by", "long-", "term", "solution", "and", "what", "does", "he", "mean", "by", "taking", "whatever", "action", "necessary", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", ",", "NNP", "NNP", "NNP", ",", "IN", "NNP", "NN", "NN", "CC", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "NN", "RB", "NN", "JJ", "."], "aSentId": 181, "answer": "Well, long-term solution meaning that once we reach a cease-fire with Hamas, they will not fire at us at the first opportunity or at the will or whenever they decide and whatever necessary means that if there is no relent to terrorizing more of half of the population of Israel, four million people under fire, we may have to consider going in, so we find ourselves, Piers, in the position of reluctant warriors, if you may.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "long-term", "solution", "meaning", "that", "once", "we", "reach", "a", "cease-fire", "with", "Hamas", ",", "they", "will", "not", "fire", "at", "us", "at", "the", "first", "opportunity", "or", "at", "the", "will", "or", "whenever", "they", "decide", "and", "whatever", "necessary", "means", "that", "if", "there", "is", "no", "relent", "to", "terrorizing", "more", "of", "half", "of", "the", "population", "of", "Israel", ",", "four", "million", "people", "under", "fire", ",", "we", "may", "have", "to", "consider", "going", "in", ",", "so", "we", "find", "ourselves", ",", "Piers", ",", "in", "the", "position", "of", "reluctant", "warriors", ",", "if", "you", "may", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Netanyahu"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "VBZ", "JJ", "CC", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", "WDT", "RB", "VBZ", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", ",", "IN", "DT", "DT", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "CC", "JJ", "NN", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", ",", "DT", "RBS", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 183, "question": "What do you say to that?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "say", "to", "that", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "TO", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 184, "answer": "Well, I say that this is tongue-in-cheek and in fact, Israel which really is the only Western country with a real democratic regime, with all the checks and balances and free press, we are the most humane, the most compassionate.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "say", "that", "this", "is", "tongue-in-cheek", "and", "in", "fact", ",", "Israel", "which", "really", "is", "the", "only", "Western", "country", "with", "a", "real", "democratic", "regime", ",", "with", "all", "the", "checks", "and", "balances", "and", "free", "press", ",", "we", "are", "the", "most", "humane", ",", "the", "most", "compassionate", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBZ", "IN", "IN", "CD", "VBD", "VBN", ",", "IN", "CD", "IN", "PRP", "VBD", "VBN", "NNS", ",", "IN", "CD", "CC", "JJR", "IN", "DT", "VBD", "RB", "VBN", "."], "qSentId": 187, "question": "Do you know how many Palestinians you've killed in the last eight days?", "question_tokens": ["Do", "you", "know", "how", "many", "Palestinians", "you", "'ve", "killed", "in", "the", "last", "eight", "days", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "PRP", "VB", "WRB", "JJ", "NNS", "PRP", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 188, "answer": "Well, it seems like about 120 were killed, about 60 of them were known terrorists, about 60 or less than that were unfortunately uninvolved.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "it", "seems", "like", "about", "120", "were", "killed", ",", "about", "60", "of", "them", "were", "known", "terrorists", ",", "about", "60", "or", "less", "than", "that", "were", "unfortunately", "uninvolved", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"TIME": ["last night"]}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 206, "question": "What will it take for you to launch a ground invasion now, do you think?", "question_tokens": ["What", "will", "it", "take", "for", "you", "to", "launch", "a", "ground", "invasion", "now", ",", "do", "you", "think", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "MD", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "RB", ",", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 207, "answer": "Well, we hope for a cease-fire last night.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "hope", "for", "a", "cease-fire", "last", "night", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"DATE": ["Wednesday"], "ORGANIZATION": ["Piers", "Hamas"], "LOCATION": ["Israel"]}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "VBN", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", ",", "CC", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", ",", "NNP", ",", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NN", "VBN", "WRB", "NNP", "VBD", "RP", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "IN", "NNP", "IN", "NNP", "."], "qSentId": 233, "question": "How do you personally feel about the indiscriminate firing of rockets into Israeli civilian areas going back months and years?", "question_tokens": ["How", "do", "you", "personally", "feel", "about", "the", "indiscriminate", "firing", "of", "rockets", "into", "Israeli", "civilian", "areas", "going", "back", "months", "and", "years", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "VBP", "PRP", "RB", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBG", "IN", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "JJ", "NNS", "VBG", "RB", "NNS", "CC", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 234, "answer": "Well, we always have said that we do not condone violence from any side, but you have to keep in mind, Piers, that this current cycle of violence started when Israel took out a military commander of Hamas on Wednesday.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "we", "always", "have", "said", "that", "we", "do", "not", "condone", "violence", "from", "any", "side", ",", "but", "you", "have", "to", "keep", "in", "mind", ",", "Piers", ",", "that", "this", "current", "cycle", "of", "violence", "started", "when", "Israel", "took", "out", "a", "military", "commander", "of", "Hamas", "on", "Wednesday", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Gaza"]}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "JJ", "NN", "WP", "PRP", "VBP", "VBG", "IN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", "IN", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "CC", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBN", "JJ", "IN", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "IN", "IN", "DT", "NNP", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 242, "question": "Why shouldn't they defend themselves by taking him out?", "question_tokens": ["Why", "should", "n't", "they", "defend", "themselves", "by", "taking", "him", "out", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "MD", "RB", "PRP", "VBP", "PRP", "IN", "VBG", "PRP", "RP", "."], "aSentId": 243, "answer": "Well, that particular person whom you are talking about was also instrumental in concluding the idea that the release of the Israeli soldier a year ago and he has been instrumental at working to calm the situation down in the Gaza strip.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "that", "particular", "person", "whom", "you", "are", "talking", "about", "was", "also", "instrumental", "in", "concluding", "the", "idea", "that", "the", "release", "of", "the", "Israeli", "soldier", "a", "year", "ago", "and", "he", "has", "been", "instrumental", "at", "working", "to", "calm", "the", "situation", "down", "in", "the", "Gaza", "strip", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "PRP", "VBD", "PDT", "DT", "JJ", "."], "qSentId": 274, "question": "A day that promised so much, but in the end delivered very little, what is your reading of where we are with this?", "question_tokens": ["A", "day", "that", "promised", "so", "much", ",", "but", "in", "the", "end", "delivered", "very", "little", ",", "what", "is", "your", "reading", "of", "where", "we", "are", "with", "this", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "WDT", "VBN", "RB", "RB", ",", "CC", "IN", "DT", "NN", "VBD", "RB", "JJ", ",", "WP", "VBZ", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "WRB", "PRP", "VBP", "IN", "DT", "."], "aSentId": 275, "answer": "Well, I don't think it promised all that much.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "I", "do", "n't", "think", "it", "promised", "all", "that", "much", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "IN", "PRP", "VBP", "DT", "NN", "NN", "NN", "TO", "PRP", ",", "PRP", "VBP", "TO", "VB", "IN", "PRP", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 294, "question": "How else do they tackle Hamas and its firing of missiles?", "question_tokens": ["How", "else", "do", "they", "tackle", "Hamas", "and", "its", "firing", "of", "missiles", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WRB", "RB", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "NNP", "CC", "PRP$", "NN", "IN", "NNS", "."], "aSentId": 295, "answer": "Well, if you want a long- term solution to it, you have to deal with it at the political level.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "if", "you", "want", "a", "long-", "term", "solution", "to", "it", ",", "you", "have", "to", "deal", "with", "it", "at", "the", "political", "level", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"ORGANIZATION": ["Hamas"]}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["DT", "NN", "VBZ", "TO", "VB", "IN", "DT", "."], "qSentId": 310, "question": "That is the way it's going to have to be?", "question_tokens": ["That", "is", "the", "way", "it", "'s", "going", "to", "have", "to", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["DT", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "PRP", "VBZ", "VBG", "TO", "VB", "TO", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 311, "answer": "A lot has to happen before that.", "answer_tokens": ["A", "lot", "has", "to", "happen", "before", "that", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {"PERSON": ["Abbas"]}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "JJ", "NNS", "IN", ",", "PRP", "VBD", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NNP", "NNP", ":", "NNP", "NNP", "CC", "PRP", "VBD", "TO", "VB", "DT", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 325, "question": "What do you think the big-picture solution could be?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "think", "the", "big-picture", "solution", "could", "be", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "MD", "VB", "."], "aSentId": 326, "answer": "Well, several weeks ago, I had occasion to meet with Prime Minister -- President Abbas and I tried to break the deadlock.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "several", "weeks", "ago", ",", "I", "had", "occasion", "to", "meet", "with", "Prime", "Minister", "--", "President", "Abbas", "and", "I", "tried", "to", "break", "the", "deadlock", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "VB", "DT", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "EX", "VBZ", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NNP", "NN", "TO", "VB", "IN", "NN", "IN", "NN", "."], "qSentId": 333, "question": "Reza Aslan, is that a good solution?", "question_tokens": ["Reza", "Aslan", ",", "is", "that", "a", "good", "solution", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["NNP", "NNP", ",", "VBZ", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 334, "answer": "I don't see any reason to think that there is any desire on the part of the current Israeli government to pursue that kind of policy.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "do", "n't", "see", "any", "reason", "to", "think", "that", "there", "is", "any", "desire", "on", "the", "part", "of", "the", "current", "Israeli", "government", "to", "pursue", "that", "kind", "of", "policy", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["NNP", ",", "PRP", "MD", "VB", "IN", "DT", "JJ", "CC", "NN", "NN", "WDT", "VBZ", "VBN", "CC", "NN", "IN", "PRP", "."], "qSentId": 359, "question": "What do you make in the way that debate just happened?", "question_tokens": ["What", "do", "you", "make", "in", "the", "way", "that", "debate", "just", "happened", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["WP", "VBP", "PRP", "VB", "IN", "DT", "NN", "IN", "NN", "RB", "VBD", "."], "aSentId": 360, "answer": "Well, you can look at the past and lament everything that's happened and complain about it.", "answer_tokens": ["Well", ",", "you", "can", "look", "at", "the", "past", "and", "lament", "everything", "that", "'s", "happened", "and", "complain", "about", "it", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {}}, {"answer_ne_tagged": {}, "docId": "121120pmt", "answer_pos_tagged": ["PRP", "VBP", "RB", "."], "qSentId": 375, "question": "Does that put more pressure now on the leaders of Israel and the Palestinians to come together and bang their heads together, get a deal done?", "question_tokens": ["Does", "that", "put", "more", "pressure", "now", "on", "the", "leaders", "of", "Israel", "and", "the", "Palestinians", "to", "come", "together", "and", "bang", "their", "heads", "together", ",", "get", "a", "deal", "done", "?"], "question_pos_tagged": ["VBZ", "IN", "NN", "JJR", "NN", "RB", "IN", "DT", "NNS", "IN", "NNP", "CC", "DT", "NNPS", "TO", "VB", "RP", "CC", "NN", "PRP$", "NNS", "RB", ",", "VB", "DT", "NN", "NN", "."], "aSentId": 376, "answer": "I think so.", "answer_tokens": ["I", "think", "so", "."], "question_ne_tagged": {"LOCATION": ["Israel"]}}]